an end-to-end example of a customer service assistant.
一个端到端的客户服务助手示例。
We'll go through the following steps.
我们将执行以下步骤：
First, we'll check the input to see if it flags the moderation API.
首先，我们会检查输入内容，看
是否触发了内容审核 API。
And four, we'll answer the user question with the model.
第四，我们将用模型回答用户的问题。
And finally, we'll put the answer through the moderation API.
最后，我们会将答案通过内容审核 API检查。
So we have our setup.
我们已经有了相关设置。
We have this additional import.
这里新增了一个额外的引用。
This is a Python package we'll use for a chatbot UI.
这是一个用于聊天机器人界面的Python包。
And so I'm going to paste in a function process_user_message.
我要粘贴一个处理用户消息的函数。
And I'm actually going to run an example first, and then we'll talk through the function.
实际上，我先运行一个例子，然
后我们再讨论这个函数。
So we have our user input that we've been using.
这是一段我们一直在使用的用户输入：
Tell me about the SmartX pro phone and the camera.
“告诉我关于SmartX pro手机和相机的信息。
So let's run this.
那我们来运行这个。
First, let's run this.
首先，我们来运行这个。
So as you can see, we're going through the steps to answer the user question.
正如你所看到的，我们正在通过
这些步骤来回答用户的问题。
So the first step, the moderation step.
第一步是审核步骤。
The second step is extracting the list of products.
第二步是提取产品列表。
The third step is looking up the product information.
第三步是查找产品信息。
And so now with this product information, the model is trying to answer the question,
现在有了这些产品信息，模
型正试图回答这个问题，
as we've seen in the previous videos.
正如我们在之前的视频中看到的。
And then finally, it puts the response through the moderation API again to make sure it's safe to show to the user.
最后，它再次通过审核API处理返回结果，
以确保对用户展示的内容是安全的。
And so this is the response that we're now familiar with.
这就是我们现在熟悉的返回结果。
And so let's talk through a little bit of what's happening.
让我们浏览一下代码看这里发生了什么。
So we have our helper function process_user_message.
有一个辅助函数process_user_message。
Takes in the user input, which is the current message, and an array of all of the messages so far.
它接收用户输入，即当前消息，以及
到目前为止的所有消息数组。
And this is when we build the chatbot UI.
这就是我们构建聊天机器人界面的时候。
So the first step, checking to see if the input flags the moderation API.
首先，检查输入是否触发了审查API。
We covered this in a previous video.
我们在之前的视频中讲过这个。
If the input is flagged, then we tell the user that we can't process the request.
如果输入被标记，那么告诉用
户我们无法处理这个请求。
If it is not flagged, we try to extract the list of products, as we did in the previous video.
如果没有被标记，尝试提取产品列
表，就像在之前的视频中那样。
Then we try to look up the products.
然后尝试查找产品。
And in this case, if no products are found, this will just be an empty string.
在这种情况下，如果没有找到产
品，这将只是一个空字符串。
Then we answer the user question.
然后我们回答用户的问题。
And then we run this response through the moderation API.
然后我们将这个返回结果通过审核 API检查。
If it's flagged, we tell the user that we can't provide this information.
如果被标记，我们会告诉用户
我们无法提供这个信息。
Maybe we'll say something, "Let me connect you to a human."
也许我们会说一些类似，“让
我帮你转接人工服务。”
And you could take some subsequent step.
然后你可以采取一些后续步骤。
And so let's put this all together with a nice UI and try to have a conversation.
让我们用一个漂亮的界面把这些都
整合起来，试着进行一次对话。
So here we have a function that will just accumulate the messages as we interact with the assistant.
这里有一个功能，只要我们与助手互
动，这些消息就会被累积起来。
And feel free to pause the video to understand in more detail how this works.
请随时暂停视频，以更详细
地了解这是如何工作的。
And of course, feel free to do the same for the really long process user message function
当然，对刚才非常长的处理用户消息功能的那
部分，您也可以一样随时暂停去详细了解。
that we just saw as well.
So now we're going to paste in our code to display the chatbot UI.
现在我们要粘贴代码来显示聊天机器人界面。
So let's ask, "What TVs do you have?"
那我们问一下：“你们有哪些电视？”
And under the hood, the assistant is going through all of the steps in the process user message function.
在后台，助手正在执行处理用
户消息功能中的所有步骤。
So it's listed a variety of different TVs.
它列出了各种不同的电视。
So now let's ask, "Which is the cheapest?"
现在我们再问：“哪个最便宜？”
Again, it's going through all the same steps, but this time it's passing the conversation history as well into the prompts.
同样，它还在执行所有相同的步骤，但这次
它还将历史会话一起传递到Prompt中。
Okay, so it's telling us that this speaker is the cheapest TV-related product we have.
好的，它告诉我们这个扬声器是我们拥
有的最便宜的与电视相关的产品。
Interesting.
有意思。
So the most expensive TV is the Cineview 8K TV.
最贵的电视是 Cineview 8K 电视。
So let's ask for more information about it.
那我们来了解更多关于它的信息吧。
Tell me more about it.
跟我说说更多关于它的事。
And so we've received some more information about this television.
我们收到了关于这台电视的更多信息。
So in this example, we've combined the techniques we've learned throughout the course to create
在这个例子中，我们将在课程中
学到的技巧结合起来，创建了
a comprehensive system with a chain of steps that evaluates user inputs, processes them,
一个包含一系列步骤的综合系统，
用于评估用户输入、处理它们，
and then checks the output.
然后检查输出。
By monitoring the quality of the system across a larger number of inputs,
通过监控更多输入的系统质量，
you can alter the steps and improve the overall performance of your system.
你可以改变步骤，提高系统的整体性能。
Maybe we might find that our prompts could be better for some of the steps.
也许会发现我们的Prompt在某
些步骤上可以做得更好。
You will find a better retrieval method, and so on.
你会找到更好的检索方法，等等。
We'll discuss this more in the next video.
我们将在下一个视频中进一步讨论这个问题。